class WritingViewModel {
  int score = 0;

  List<Map> questions = [
    {
      'question': 'She works ---- Saturday.',
      'answers': ['at', 'to', 'in', 'on'],
      'correctAnswer': 'on',
    },
    {
      'question': 'I stay at home ---- the morning.',
      'answers': ['at', 'to', 'in', 'on'],
      'correctAnswer': 'in',
    },
    {
      'question': 'How do you get to work? ----.',
      'answers': ['By car', 'In car', 'By the car', 'On car'],
      'correctAnswer': 'By car',
    },
    {
      'question': 'Do you like classical music? ----.',
      'answers': ['Yes, I likes', 'Yes, I like', 'Yes, I does', 'Yes, I do'],
      'correctAnswer': 'Yes, I do',
    },
    {
      'question': '---- you ever visited London?',
      'answers': ['Did', 'Do', 'Were', 'Have'],
      'correctAnswer': 'Have',
    },
    {
      'question': 'She has never ---- to New York.',
      'answers': ['gone', 'was', 'been', 'went'],
      'correctAnswer': 'been',
    },
    {
      'question': 'He passed his English exam very ----.',
      'answers': ['easy', 'easier', 'good', 'easily'],
      'correctAnswer': 'easily',
    },
    {
      'question': 'He ---- born in 1963 in America.',
      'answers': ['had', 'is', 'was', 'did'],
      'correctAnswer': 'was',
    },
    {
      'question': 'Switzerland is ---- than Britain.',
      'answers': ['as small', 'smallest', 'more small', 'smaller'],
      'correctAnswer': 'smaller',
    },
    {
      'question': 'When ---- you go to the USA? Last year.',
      'answers': ['did', 'was', 'went', 'have'],
      'correctAnswer': 'did',
    },
  ];
}